<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

	<string name="help_wallet">
<![CDATA[
		<p>
			The upper left part of the screen displays your selected Bitcoin address that other people need to know in order to send you Bitcoins.
			Tap to change the address.
		</p>
		<p>
			The QR code on the right contains your bitcoin address and can be used for scanning by another party.
			Tap on the QR code to get a larger version of it.
		</p>
		<p>
			In the middle of the screen, your balance is displayed.
			The value of your wallet is also shown in one selected local currency.
			Tap on balance to display list of all local currencies, and tap on one of the currencies to select it as default.
		</p>
		<p>
			The bottom of the screen is covered by your transactions list, which is empty at the beginning.
			Pending transactions are greyed out until they are confirmed.
			Tap on one entry to add the senders or receivers address to the address book.
			Swipe left or right to apply filters to the list.
		</p>
		<p>
			You can send or request coins by tapping the buttons in the action bar.
			More options are available in the options menu.
		</p>
	]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_request_coins">
<![CDATA[
		<p>
			Using this dialog, you can request coins from another person (who should already have installed Bitcoin Wallet).
		</p>
		<p>
			First, you can enter an amount of Bitcoins to request.
		</p>
		<p>
			Then, you either have the generated QR code scanned by the other person.
			Or, you can send your request to a remote person with the share button in the action bar.
			The other person will have to click the Bitcoin URL.
		</p>
		<p>
			Either way, the other person will be presented a dialog for sending coins with all fields pre-populated.
			If she accepts, all she needs to do is sending the payment.
		</p>
	]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_send_coins">
<![CDATA[
		<p>
			You have initiated the process of sending coins.
			You came here either through the main screen or by clicking on a Bitcoin URL in your mobile browser.
		</p>
		<p>
			First, you enter the Bitcoin address to pay to.
			The address will autocomplete from known entries in your address book.
			You can also scan QR codes with Bitcoin addresses or Bitcoin requests by pressing the QR button in the action bar.
		</p>
		<p>
			Next, you can see how many Bitcoins you can spend at the moment.
			Any difference to the balance from the main screen is still unconfirmed and can thus not yet be spent.
		</p>
		<p>
			Last, you enter the amount to pay.
		</p>
		<p>
			You can enter a payment while being offline.
			It will be sent on next restart of Bitcoin Wallet.
			If you want a payment to be processed as fast as possible, make sure you are well connected (i.e. on a WLAN).
		</p>
		<p>
			Note:
			Payments are irreversible!
			Always check the receiving address.
		</p>
	]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_safety">
<![CDATA[
		<p><b>Hints and Tips</b></p>
		<p>
			The tips below are important. If you are new to Bitcoin, please read them carefully.
			More details and helpful information can be found on our website www.kncwallet.com
		</p>
		<p>
			Please write down your wallet backup password, we cannot recover this. KnC do not keep copies of your wallet or any of your passwords or PINs.
		</p>
		<p>Bitcoins are stored on your phone. If you lose your phone you may lose your Bitcoins!</p>
		<p>
			Always create a backup of your private keys and store them somewhere safe. This can be Cloud Storage such as a Dropbox account or Google Drive and you should always choose a strong password for your key backup. You can do this easily from the settings page in the KnC Wallet.
		</p>
		<p>
			Only carry small amounts of Bitcoin on your phone, treat them like physical cash, just carry what you need for a day.
		</p>
		<p>Before you uninstall or delete your app data, remember to move your Bitcoins to another wallet first as deleting your app data will delete your Bitcoins!</p>
		<p>Use a PIN to protect your phone and your KnC Wallet. You can enable the KnC Wallet pin in the settings page.</p>
		<p>Finally, have fun with Bitcoin!</p>
		<p>For full terms and conditions of use, please see www.kncwallet.com</p>
	]]>
	</string>

</resources>